{"data":[{"question":"_______ his parents is British. He is French and she is Spanish.","a":"Either of","b":"Neither of","c":"Neither","d":"Either","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neither of= no one of two","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The house was ________ large and comfortable.","a":"both","b":"either","c":"neither","d":"none","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The two boys? No, I haven't seen ________ them.","a":"either of","b":"either","c":"neither","d":"none of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Either of : one or the other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The cave was ________ cold and wet.","a":"neither","b":"either","c":"none","d":"both","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Is that Mr Dumas, the writer?' 'Yes, _________ father _________ son are writers.'","a":"both\/and","b":"either\/or","c":"either\/and","d":"neither\/nor","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Both...and: used to emphasize that something is true not just of one person, thing, or situation but also of another ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We _______ knew the answer. It was very easy.","a":"neither","b":"either","c":"all","d":"none","answer":"3","explain":"\n- All: every one of us","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She tried both keys but _______ fitted the lock.","a":"either","b":"neither","c":"nor","d":"both","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neither: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We _________ got the geometry problem right.","a":"neither","b":"all","c":"none of","d":"both","answer":"2","explain":"\n- All: every one of us","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The two windows were open. _______ them had been forced.","a":"Both","b":"Neither","c":"Both of","d":"None","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I tried two jackets but neither ________ the right size.","a":"was","b":"has","c":"had","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither was: none of two jackets have the right size","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}